wikiworldbook.com 2012-10-04

# Privacy Policy - WikiWorldBook

##### Policy Effective:- 16 May 2008

WikiWorldBook Limited (WWB) is committed to protecting the privacy of all visitors to its website, WikiWorldBook.com (the Site). Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us. We may update our privacy policy from time to time without giving you notice, so please check it each time you visit the Site. The date of the most recent revision will appear at the top of this page.

**Whenever you give us personal data, you are consenting to its collection and use in accordance with this privacy policy, including our use of cookies as explained below.**

## What personal data do we collect?

When you register your profile on the WikiWorldBook global address book you will be asked to provide certain information about yourself including your name and contact details. We may also collect information about your usage of the Site as well as information from messages, blogs or reviews you post to the Site and e-mails or letters you send to us.

We also automatically collect data about visitors to the Site by using cookies.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of data or message that is sent from a web server to your browser and is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies make it easier and faster for you to log on to and use the site during future visits. They also allow us to monitor website traffic and to personalise the content of the Site for you.

You can reset your browser so as not to accept cookies and to alert you when a cookie is sent, although, in that case, you may not be able to use certain features on the Site.

## Where do we store your personal data?

The information you provide to us will be held on our computers in the United Kingdom and may be accessed by or given to our staff working within the UK, or our consultants in the European Union and the USA.

When you give us personal data, that data may be sent electronically to servers anywhere in the world and may be used, stored and processed anywhere in the world, including countries outside the European Economic Area. Bear in mind that such countries do not always have strong data protection laws. However, whenever and wherever we collect, process or use personal data we will always take steps to ensure that it is treated securely and in accordance with this policy.

## How do we use your Personal Data?

Your information will enable us to provide you with access to relevant parts of the Site and to supply the information that you have requested and deal with your enquiry. We may also use and analyse the information we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop our services. We do not use this information to build a personal profile of you.

If you have given your consent (please see your Privacy Settings in “Update Profile” on your profile page), we may notify you occasionally about important changes or developments to the Site or our services. WWB reserves the right to send you notices about your account, even though you opt out of all voluntary email notifications, although these will be rare and extraordinary occurrences.

We will not use your personal data for marketing purposes without obtaining your permission first (and before we collect your personal data). Please also note that the advertising on the Site is automatically generated from the information on the page, so it might use your content or data to do this, but it will do so anonymously and indiscriminately.

## To whom might we disclose your personal data?

We may disclose your personal data to third parties who process information and provide services on our behalf including responding to and following up your enquiries. Some of those third parties may be located outside the United Kingdom, but will only act for us for the purposes set out in this policy or for other purposes approved by you.

We may also pass aggregate information on the usage of our site to third parties, but this will not include information that can be used to identify you.

If you post or otherwise make available offensive, inappropriate or objectionable content anywhere on the Site, or otherwise engage in any disruptive behaviour on Site, we may use your personal information to stop such behaviour.

Where WWB reasonably believes that you are or may be in breach of any of the laws of England or Wales (e.g. because content you have posted may be defamatory or infringe intellectual property rights), WWB may use your personal information to inform relevant third parties such as your employer, e-mail/Internet provider or law enforcement agencies about the material and your behaviour.

Unless we are required or allowed to do so by law, we will not otherwise share, sell or distribute any of your personal information without your consent.

## Security

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet or any other network can be guaranteed as 100% secure, but we employ appropriate security measures to try to protect your information from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage.,

## Accessing and Updating

Individuals have certain rights of access to their personal data including the rights to see the information held about them and to ask that necessary changes are made to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact the Data Protection Officer at WikiWorldBook at [DPO@WikiWorldBook.com](mailto:DPO@WikiWorldBook.com) . This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it

We are entitled by law to charge a small fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

## Links to Third Party Sites

Any third party websites that you link to via the Site are not covered by our privacy policy and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We urge you to always be aware when you leave this website, to read the privacy policy of other websites and to use caution when entering personal information online.

Inclusion of a link to another web site does not constitute a recommendation or endorsement of that organisation, site or its content by WWB.

## Communication of Changes and Corrections

Any changes to our privacy policy in the future will be posted to the website and, where appropriate, notified through e-mail notification.

All comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your personal information are welcomed and should be addressed to our Data Protection Officer at [DPO@WikiWorldBook.com](mailto:DPO@WikiWorldBook.com)
